goalwin.com 2014-04-10

# GoalWin > Support > Privacy Policy

## Privacy policy

Goalwin is committed to maintaining the privacy and security of personal information relating to all visitors of the website www.goalwin.com provides your personal data for access and registration. Our privacy policy meets the current needs of visitors who want to know what personal information we store, because we are doing so, and its actual use; in accordance with the provisions of the European Parliament on data protection (Directive CE 95/46/EC) and confidentiality of electronic communications (Directive CE/2002/58/EC), we will endeavor to keep your personal information secure at all times through the implementation of appropriate technical and organizational controls. Please take a moment to read the following policy to learn how to manage your personal information, such as the use of our services and then accept its terms.

**The aim of the collection of personal information**  
We collect and use personal information to meet legal and regulatory requirements, for historical and statistical purpose; for security and control; to provide our services, and to provide more services in the future. Occasionally, we may use your personal information to contact you via mail, email, telephone or mobile phone and to get you to know our products or events, activities, projects, plans, developments, businesses and special offers being promoted or incurred by the Company. Providing your information states that its use occurs in accordance with the privacy policy and does not constitute a violation of its rights as configured in the Data Protection Act (Chapter 440 of the Laws of Malta). We invite you to contact us at any time if you do not wish to receive promotional material or advertising.

**Disclosure of personal information to third parties**  
The Company will not disclose customer information to third parties, except to technical employees of the companies who necessarily have legal access to provide services. However, the Company may be compelled by law or legal process to report personal information to the competent authorities, in particular to the Lotteries and Gaming Authority.

**Protection of personal information**  
The Company protects the security of data that users send, using appropriate physical, electronic and management processes. It is used SSL encryption on the site for transmission of sensitive data and to communicate with our payment system. Please note that we cannot guarantee that all data transmitted over the Internet is completely secure. Therefore, we invite you to take every precaution to protect your personal information when you are on the Internet.

**Access to personal information**  
You have right of access to information we have about you. To review and update personal contact information, simply access our site with your username and password or through the page, My Account, where you can edit the information. If you prefer, you can contact the Customer Service using the details available on the site. Moreover, you have the right to correct any inaccurate information, and if necessary obtain the cancellation. We have the right to require a written request regarding the information we maintain.
